Good men can do bad things.
The Hollow Point is a action, drama, thriller film
directed by Gonzalo López-Gallego.
Los Reyes County, Arizona.
Leland, a retired lawman, works with Wallace, the new sheriff who replaces him, when a
vicious hit man, sent by a Mexican drug cartel, threatens their border small town.
Wallace, played by Patrick Wilson.
Leland, played by Ian McShane.
Atticus, played by John Leguizamo.
Marla, played by Lynn Collins.
Shepard, played by Jim Belushi.
Lilly, played by Karli Hall.
The Hollow Point is a 2016 American Western film directed by
Gonzalo López-Gallego and written by Nils Lyew.
The film stars Patrick Wilson, Lynn Collins, Ian McShane,
John Leguizamo, Jim Belushi and Michael Flynn.
The film was released on December 16, 2016, by Vertical Entertainment.
The film explores themes of hitman, arizona, drug
cartel, used car salesman, crooked sheriff.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.